Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: General Correspondence, 1941-2001
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical, 1941-2001
    - Stanford University: Resignation of President Kennedy, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University: "Shine" Project, Dr. Kenneth Melmon, School of Medicine, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University: Stanford Japan Center, Kyoto, 1986-1989 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University: Tom Watson Golf Day and Seminar, 1986-1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence and a signed photograph of Tom Watson.
    - Stanford University: William Gates Computer Science Building Dedication, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University: World Economic Forum, 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Stansbury, Herb, 1990-2001 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      Includes correspondence and one photograph of Hewlett and Stansbury at the Bohemian Grove. Some material is related to Barney Oliver and SETI.
    - Stanton, Dr. Frank, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Starzl, Dr. Thomas E., 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - State Politics, 1994-1996 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence on various candidates, propositions, and bills.
    - Stearns, H. Myrl, Varian Associates, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Steele, Roger C., 1981 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Stent, Mary, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Steps, Steve, 1981-1984 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Sterling, Dr. J. E. Wallace, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Sterne, W. Eugene, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Stevens, John P., 1981 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Stewart, O. J., 1987 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Stiles, Gene, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Stillman, Timothy G., 1993 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Stocker, James D., Scott Paper Company, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Strangway, David W., University of British Columbia, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks II, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Stratmann, Erich, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Stratton, Julius A., 1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Strauss, Robert S., White House Special Counselor on Inflation, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Stretch, James E., 1983-1985 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Stromeyer, Ludwig, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Stur, Louis, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Sullivan, John F., Jr., President of Bath Iron Works Corporation, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Sullivan, Leon H., President Foundation for Education and Self-Help, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Sun Valley Company, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Swearingmen, John E., Standard Oil Company, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Swing, Reverend William E., Bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of California, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Sympathy Letters, 1981-1987 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      Includes correspondence with friends and colleagues regarding those who recently passed away. Also contains some obituaries.
    - Sympathy Letters, 1987-1989 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Sympathy Letters, 1990-1992 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Sympathy Letters, 1993-2000 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Sympathy Letters, Hewlett-Packard Employees, 1985-1989 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      Includes correspondence with friends and colleagues regarding those who recently passed away. Also contains some obituaries, and correspondence of David Packard.
    - Synergos Institute, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Talbot, Frank H., Director of National Museum of Natural History, 1989-1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Targeting Information and Reports, 1985-1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Tartaglia, Gennaro, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Harry, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, R. Perry, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Vernon "Moose", Jr., 1981-1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Technical Consulting Group, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Technologic Partners, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Technology 21 Project, Johns Hopkins University, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Technology for Communications International, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Telescope, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence with Charles Moore and Barney Oliver.
    - Television, 1992-1994 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Temple, Anice P., 1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Tenney, John A., Saint Patricks High School, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Terman Memoir, 1985-1997 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Testmobile, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Texas Instruments, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Texas Instruments Foundation, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Thomas College, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Thomas College, 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Thomas More College, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Thrower, Charles S., 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Thurston, William R., President of General Radio, 1983-1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Tilton, Cecil G., 1975 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Toothpaste Tube Wonder-Winder Invention, 1992-1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Torr, Professor Douglas, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Toth, Bryant A., 1992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Tower, Raymond C., FMC Corporation, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Townes, Charles, Oakland Museum Association, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Trans World Airlines, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Trefethen, E. E., Jr., 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Trefethen, John V., Trefethen Vineyards, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Tripp, Maurice, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Trippe, Betty, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Trippe, Blaine and Zelta, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Truche, Dominique, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Tucher, Caroyln, Palo Education School District, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Tunny, John V., Senator for the State of California, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Turner, Gray H., 1989 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Tyler, Lee, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Uhrhane, Major General F. F. (Retired), 1989 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      Uhrhane served with William Hewlett at the Pentagon during World War Two.
    - Uihlein, George H., 1981 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Uihlein, Joseph E., Jr., 1964 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Ultrasonic Intruder Detector, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified, 1984-1996, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
      Includes correspondence from unidentified people, and a photocopied photograph of Bill and Rosemary Hewlett.
    - Unique International, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - United Nations, 1992-1995 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - United States Council of the International Chamber of Commerce, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - United States Geological Survey, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - United States Government Agencies, 1972-1976 (Box 54, Folder 29)
      Includes correspondence with Henry A. Kissinger, Peter G. Peterson, the Office of Tribal Resources Development, the Office of Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, and other individuals and government agencies.
    - University of British Columbia, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - University of California Regents, 1974-1990 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - University of California, Berkeley: Chancellor Tien Lunch, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 33)
      Includes correspondence with Clark Kerr and others.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1969-1977 (Box 54, Folder 34)
      Includes correspondence with James D. Hart, Thomas F. Budinger, Charles H. Townes, A. Starker Leopold, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1978-1984 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      Includes correspondence with A. Starker Leopold, Charles H. Townes, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1985-1991 (Box 54, Folder 36)
      Includes correspondence with Donald H. Perkel, Ira Michael Heyman, David Pierpont Gardner, Bernard J. Frieden, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence with Charles H. Townes, Chang-Lin Tien, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence with Richard H. Peterson, C. D. Mote Jr., Paul R. Gray, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: General, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence with Bonnie C. Wade, Charles H. Townes, Maryellen Himmel, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, Berkeley: Glenn T. Seaborg Birthday and Endowment, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - University of California, Davis, 1973-1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence with Robert K. McCleary and T. Y. Shen.
    - University of California, Irvine: General, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence with Donald H. Perkel and J. Weber.
    - University of California, Irvine: Mayan-European Calendar, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1974-1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence with William Ouchi, John Doyle, Glenn T. Seaborg, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of California, San Diego, 1977-1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence with Robert W. Conn, Leroy Lewis, and Richard C. Atkinson.
    - University of California, San Francisco, 1974-1992 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Includes correspondence with John Lo Schiavo, Julius R. Krevans, and Alexander R. Margulis.
    - University of California, Santa Barbara, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence with L. Gary Leal.
    - University of California, Santa Cruz, 1982-1996 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      Includes correspondence with Dean E. McHenry and Robert L. Sinsheimer.
    - University of Cincinnati, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence with George Rieveschl, Jr.
    - University of Colorado, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      Includes correspondence with John Riggen.
    - University of Edinburgh, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      Includes correspondence with Sir David Smith and Donald MacQueen.
    - University of Georgia, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      Includes correspondence with Robert C. Anderson and John F. Garst.
    - University of Maryland, 1985-1998 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      Includes correspondence with Gary W. Rubloff, John S. Baras, and Nariman Farvadin.
    - University of Michigan, Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1972-1983 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence with Fred H. MacInstosh, Oliver F. Williams, Joseph C. Hogan, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of Notre Dame (part 1 of 3), 1983-1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence with Edward A. Malloy, David M. Morrisey, Oliver F. Williams, William P. Sexton, and other faculty and staff.
    - University of Notre Dame (part 2 of 3), 1983-1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - University of Notre Dame (part 3 of 3), 1983-1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1994-1999 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence with William P. Sexton, Daniel Reagan, and Edward A. Malloy.
    - University of Pennsyslvania, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence with Herb A. Navis.
    - University of Rochester, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence with W. Allen Wallis, Svend Eldup-Jordensen, and Dean Morton. Some correspondence is David Packard's.
    - University of Southern California, 1977-1997 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence with Leonard M. Silverman, Ward Edwards, and John E. Fleming.
    - University of Texas, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence with John J. McKetta and John L. Tullis.
    - University of the Pacific, 1981, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      Includes correspondence with Stanley McCaffrey and Ernest W. Wood.
    - University of Utah, 1975, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence with Charles J. Nabors and Marc E. Day.
    - University of Virginia, 1972, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Includes correspondence with Laurie Burr.
    - US News and World Report, 1972-1979 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Utah State University, 1970-1985 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence with Vern M. Buehler, Clayton Clark, Marc E. Day, and other faculty and staff.
    - Utah State University, 1986-1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence with Clayton Clark, Paul M. Norton, and others. Also includes some photographs of Utah State University's campus.
    - Utah State University, 1993, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence with Paul M. Norton and some university publications.
    - Vadetec Proposal, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Valentine, G. H., Jr., Seaboard Seed Company, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Valley Presbyterian Church, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Van Den Daele, Ysabel Durandy, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Van Der Erve, Marc, KPMG Fides Management Consulting, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Van Rensselaer, Cort, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Vanderhoeven, Fran and Gerard, 1979, 1996-1998 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Vanderwende, Richard H., 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Varon, L. N., 1983 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Vasconcellos, John, Assemblyman California Legislature, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Vaughan, Norman D., Mount Vaughan Antarctica Expedition (part 1 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Vaughan, Norman D., Mount Vaughan Antarctica Expedition (part 2 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Vaught, John L., and Hammond, Don, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Veal, Harlan K., Esquire, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Venture Magazine, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Verbic, John R., Vice President of Bessemer Trust Company, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Verbica, Peter Coe, 1986-1993 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Verbica, Robert George, 1985-1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Villalba, Chester F., Family Service Association, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      Flora Hewlett served on the board of the Family Service Association.
    - Villavicincio, Paul J., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Violins, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Virtual Computer Marketing Corporation, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Vodkas (Comparison of Quality), 1986 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Vogel, Charles, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Vogt, Helen, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Vohs, James A., 1981 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Vojtik, Carla L., National Bodyguard Network, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Volokh, Anne, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Von Clemm, Michael, 1986-1990 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      Includes correspondence with Michael Von Clemm and Robert S. Kerr III, Lieutenant Governor of Oklahoma.
    - Von Wening, Eugene, Jr., 1982 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Walker, Brooks, Jr., 1981 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Walker, Danielle, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Walker, Patricia, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Wall Street Transcript, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Wallenberg Traditional High School, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Wang, Kebin, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Ware, T. M., 1984 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Warren, Frank M., 1978, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Warren, Louis and Rosalie, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Warthin, Virginia, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Washington Advisory Council, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Watson, R. O., Hercules Incorporated, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Weaver, Harry, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Weaver, James Frederick, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Weber, Ernst, 1979-1990 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Weber, Karl C., Consul General Emeritus for Austria, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Weber, Martha, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Weber, Vernon R., 1978 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Webster, Bethuel M., 1981 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Webster, G. W., 1978 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Weigler, Jeffrey Scott, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - Weisman, Morey, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - Weller, Barton L., 1984 (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - Werkheiser, Colleen M., 1983 (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - West, Kirkland, 1979-1989 (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - Wharton School of the University of Pennsyslvania, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - Wheaton, Virginia, 1991-1993 (Box 58, Folder 48)
      Wheaton claims to have known William Hewlett's mother, Louise Redington.
    - Wheeler, Harold A., Chief Scientist of Hazeltine Corporation, 1978-1989 (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - Wheeler, R. O., 1978 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Whelan, H. Gabe, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Whelan, John D., 1981 (Box 58, Folder 52)
    - Whipp, Richard, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 53)
    - White, Betty and Howard J., 1978 (Box 58, Folder 54)
    - Whitney, Marcus B., 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 55)
    - Wickersham, Grover, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 56)
    - Wickett, Walton A., Menlo School and College, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 57)
    - Wiesner, Barbara, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - Wilbur, Dwight and Martha, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 59)
    - Wilbur, Jean, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 60)
      Includes correspondence and a photocopied photograph of the 5 Hewlett children together at a party.
    - Wilbur, Ray and Martha, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 61)
    - Wild, John, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Wild Wings, Minneapolis Gallery, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Wilkerson, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - William E. Hall and Company, Management Consultants, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Williams, E. Thomas, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Sharon, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Willis, Beverly, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Willis, Reverend Emeal, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Willoughby, Elaine, 1995-1998 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, George M., 1963, 1983, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Paul A., 1993 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Sandy, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, T. A., Chairman Emeritus of Boeing Corporation, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, William A., 1980 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Winches, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Wines, 1982-1997 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Wing Aerodynamics, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Witte, Roberta, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Witter, Peter and Susan, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Woodland, June, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Woodside Priory School, 1984, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Woolson, Steven T., 1993 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - World Economic Forum, 1991-1995 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - World Resources Institute, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Worley, Bill, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Wozniak, Steve, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 27)
      Includes a request from Wozniak for support to help his son get into Stanford, and William Hewlett's response.
    - Wright, Philip N., Jr., 1978 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Wu, Gene, Wu Corporation, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Yale University, 1973-1982 (Box 59, Folder 30)
      Includes correspondence with Wesley H. Poling, A. Bartlett Giamatti, Hanna H. Gray, and other faculty and staff.
    - Yale University, 1985-1992 (Box 59, Folder 31)
      Includes correspondence with Vernon R. Loucks Jr., John A. Wilkinson, James W. Lukens, and other faculty and staff.
    - Yale University, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Yaras, Vince, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Yokogawa, Shozo, President of Yokogawa Hokushin Electric Corporation, 1984-1993 (Box 59, Folder 34)
      Includes correspondence of both William Hewlett and David Packard. One photograph of Hewlett and two other men is present.
    - Young, John Alan, 1982-1984 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Young, Richard, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Youngs, R. L., Forest Products Laboratory, Forest Service, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Zachariah, Vic, Zack Electronics, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Zajicek, Jill, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Zarem, Dr. A. M., 1987 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Zaro, Nancy, "Portraits of Success" Project, 1995-1996 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Zeidler, Howard D., 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Zeigler, Martha and Robert, 1979, 1990-1993 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Zimmerman, Scottie, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Subseries B: Chronological, 1964-2001
    Contains carbon copies of William Hewlett's outgoing correspondence including some inter-office corespondence at Hewlett-Packard.
    Arranged chronologically.
    General
    A searchable index of all correspondence in this subseries is available in the Stanford Digital Repository at this link: http://purl.stanford.edu/tq973kf0425
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 1 of 2), 1966 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 2 of 2), 1966 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, July-December (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 1 of 2), 1971 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 2 of 2), 1971 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 1 of 2), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January-June (part 2 of 2), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January-July, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, August-December, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, July-December, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, January-June, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)